bleubloom.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy – Bleu Bloom

**Privacy Policy**

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.womensarticle.com and BleuBloom and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to BleuBloom include bleubloom.com. The BleuBloom website is a Content Website. By using the BleuBloom website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

BleuBloom may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by BleuBloom. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the BleuBloom website.

BleuBloom encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from BleuBloom so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. BleuBloom is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the BleuBloom website.

**Use of your Personal Information  **

BleuBloom only attains your email address through mailchimp.  All information is kept confidential and never shared.

**Use of Cookies**

The BleuBloom website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize BleuBloom pages, or register with BleuBloom site or services, a cookie helps BleuBloom to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same BleuBloom website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the BleuBloom features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the BleuBloom services or websites you visit.

**Children Under Thirteen**

BleuBloom does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications via their feedburner account

–

**Changes to this Statement**

BleuBloom will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. BleuBloom encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how BleuBloom is protecting your information.

Effective as of January 12, 2018
